lehmiller.com 2018-01-29

# PRIVACY — Sex And Psychology

**Sex and Psychology’s Privacy Policy**

This privacy policy applies only to information collected by Sex and Psychology (http://sexandpsychology.com). It describes what personally identifying information we collect, how we use it, with whom it can be shared, and what choices you have in how we collect and use your data.

 **Collection, Use, and Sharing of Personal Information**

We only collect personal information provided voluntarily by website users via online forms or email (e.g., signing up for our mailing list, e-mailing us a question). Only Sex and Psychology will have access to this information. We will not share this information with third parties.

If you sign up for the mailing list, you will receive occasional email newsletters. If you email us, your contact information will be used to get in touch with you regarding your request.

 **Your Options**

Because we only collect personal information provided voluntarily, you are in complete control of what (if any) information we have access to.

Should you provide us with your contact information and wish to opt out of future communications, you can do so at any time. An “unsubscribe” link is provided in each email newsletter, but you can also contact us using the online form or email address provided on our website under the “[Questions, Media Requests, and Advertising](http://www.lehmiller.com/ask-a-question/)” tab.

 **Links**

Links to other sites are included on our website. Please be advised that we are not responsible for the content or privacy policies of any linked sites. Keep this in mind when you leave our site and be sure to consult other websites' privacy statements to stay informed of their policies and your rights.

 **Cookies**  

Like most websites, we use "cookies." A cookie is small piece of text sent to your internet browser that allows us to do things such as identify repeat visitors and track site usage patterns. You can change how cookies are handled by your device within your browser settings. 

 **Surveys and Contests**

Occasionally, Sex and Psychology may collect information for reader surveys or contests. Your participation is always voluntary and disclosure of any information is entirely your choice.

Information requested may sometimes include contact information (e.g., email address), demographic information (e.g., age, gender identity, etc.), and survey questions pertaining to various aspects of sex and psychology.

In such instances, contact information will be used as needed in order to alert contest winners. Survey information will be used to monitor and improve user satisfaction with the site. Survey data may also be used to develop future blog posts or infographics that will be of interest to readers of the site; however, no personally identifiable information will be used in the creation of such blog posts or infographics.

 **Updates**

This privacy policy may change from time to time. Updates will be posted to this page.
